新婚
-1
krusty：晚8点恢复直播
从现在起我会准守奥斯卡评选规则的
D'oh!
不
In a world,
这个世界里
in a hemisphere,in a continent, in a country,
这个半球，这个大陆，这个国家
in a state, in a city,in a neighborhood,
这个州，这个城市，这个邻居
in a street, in a house,in a living room,
这个街，这个房子，这个客厅
five heroes would be called.
5个英雄将被召唤
To tackle the most dangerousquest of their lives.
接受生命中最危险的任务
Let's sit on that couch.
来抢沙发吧
They're in.
他们中套了
这个 时间 它 不 适合 去 坐
这个沙发不是很舒服
And in retrospect,city officials regret holding
回顾起来，政府官员们后悔把持了
the gang truce negotiations at Santa's Village.
停战协议，在圣诞村。
In other news,we're about to go live
下条新闻，我们来连接
to Mr. Burns' announcement of his annual rate hike.
burns先生的年度加息
Springfielders are about to find out how much
春田镇的人们找出了
their electricity bills will go up.
他们该上涨多少电费
I'm being told that Mr. Burns is approaching the lectern now.
我正在链接burns先生，现在他正靠近讲台
Apparently there are a few stairs he's struggling to climb.
很明显，由于没有梯子他攀爬的很幸苦
He's up the stairs but is now being buffeted by the breeze.
他上了梯子但是现在正和微风搏斗
And they've put some rocks in his pocket and...
所以他们放了些石头在他口袋里并且。。
we're ready to go.
我开始直播吧
To decide how much your electricity bills will rise,
为了解决该涨多少电费
I've assembled a team of distinguished economists
我已经召集了一个卓越的经济团队
and placed plausible rate hike percentages on their backs.
并且在他们背后有合理的加息百分比
Now we will use unfettered free market principles
现在我们将解除市场自由调控
to arrive at a number.
来提升数值
Release the hounds.
放狗
Notice how the Keynesians climb trees
告诉Keynesians怎么爬树
while the Austrian school economists hide under rocks.
当奥地利经济学家躲在石头后
That is fascinating.
多有趣啊
And there you have it,folks, rates will rise
你们该知晓了，大家，利息将会提到
a healthy 17%.
一个健康的17%
And now, to help you disperse...
现在，散会
Let me guess, you're going to release the hounds again.
让我猜猜，你又要放狗了
Oh, don't be silly.
哦，别傻了
Release the radioactive steam.
释放放射性气体
Electricity costs are going up 17%.
电费将涨17%
This station can't afford that.
电视台才不支付呢
We're barely keeping the lights on as it is.
我们就像这样保持灯亮
I know it's a kid's show,
这是个儿童节目
but I got to see you topless.
我想看看不穿衣的你
This isn't your dressing room.
这不是你的衣服间
I know, but the monkey's got a girl
我知道，但是那猴子和一个女孩
in my dressing room.
在我衣物间
The decision to pull the plug is never easy.
话说这是很艰难的决定对于插着插销
Particularly with the 17% rate hike.
要特别加收17%的利息
Do I get a vote?
我投票了吗
That's just air escaping his lungs.
刚才是他肺漏气了
Oh, I guess we'll be peeling our shrimp by hand this year.
哦，我猜这一年我们得手动去虾皮了
We can keep the shrimp de-veiner, though, right?
我们可以保留虾皮机，虽然，行不
I'm afraid not.
我恐怕不行
And this goes, too.
这个也改扔了
When I found out shrimp cocktails had no alcohol,
当我发现虾尾酒没有酒精时
I really lost interest.
我就已经失去兴趣了
Children, we can no longer afford
孩子们，我们不再有能力支付
to use anything electric.
任何一个电器了。
However, we will still be able to watch today's film,
然而，我们仍然能看今天的教育片
thanks to the magic of potato power.
感谢魔力的土豆能源吧
Sometimes Y: the story of a vowel that goes both ways.
关于Y：这是个原音故事教你两种方式
Emergency meeting in the faculty lounge. BYOB.
紧急会议在教室休息室，自带酒水
Well, class,I don't mind leaving you,
好吧，孩子们，离开你们我才不担心呢
because one of you is my spy.
因为在你当中我安排了个五道杠
You said you weren't going to tell.
你说过你不会这么说的
Oh, wait, you didn't.
哦，等等，你们别
So no one knows who the Milhouse is.
好吧，没人会知道，就是milhouse的
The school is broke.
学校瘫痪了
I had to sell all the trombone mutes.
我们必须卖掉所有的长号调音器
Why did I sell one to Nelson?
我干嘛会卖给nelson一个
Hmm. Sounds better than half the kids in the band.
嗯，听起来不错相比一半的孩子乐队
So does a leaf blower.
嗯，该弄个鼓风机了
Look, the district can't afford to keep every school open,
看啊，这地方已经不能支付学校的开支
so all the kids will take a standardized test.
因此所有的学生都得标准化测试了
Whichever school scores the lowest will be closed forever.
对于最差分数的学校，关门大吉了
So you're saying, if our kids don't pass this test,
也就是所，如果孩子们不能通过这个测试
you're shutting down Springfield Elementary?
春田小学将会倒闭
I don't teach to the test.I teach 'em to dodge balls.
我没教他们考试，但我教他们躲避球了
Things they can use in life.
这个在他们的人生中才有用
How is that useful?
躲避球有啥用
Ow.
啊
We all came here to avoid scrutiny.
我们来这是为了避开监察
Who else would hire a lunch lady
谁还会雇佣一个午餐女
accused of poisoning her husband?
毒害过他丈夫
Never convicted.
可没判有罪啊
They couldn't find the body.
他们没发现尸体
Anyone care for some chicken-Pete pie?
谁会关心pete鸡肉陷派呢
Did you say "chicken-Pete pie"?
你说pete鸡肉派？
His friends called him Pete.
他的朋友叫他pete
Good-bye, my electrical friends.
再见，我的电器朋友
I can't afford to use you,so I'm doing what any good
我承担不起你们，所以做你想做的吧
American would do:throw you away.
美国人会这样做：把你扔了
And it still works.
还可以工作
This could come in handy.
这个可以派上用场
Ah, ah, ah, but let me check that list of things
哈哈，让我看看做事清单
Marge said never to bring home.
marge说别再带回家了
Dogs, cats, octopuses,octopi, octopuseseseses.
狗，猫，章鱼，章，章鱼鱼
Parking meter,you're working for me now.
停车计价表，你现在为我工作了
Mannequin heads,you're working for me now.
时装模特的头，你们现在为我工作了。
Lot of people at the dump today.
今天好多人在垃圾堆啊
The proctors are here.
学监们来了
Their leader seems to be a woman.
他们的头看起来是个女的
Catalog poses.
摆造型
When will they finish grading those tests?
什么时候他们能考完
I hate waiting; that's why I hate risotto.
我讨厌等，这就是为什么我讨厌意大利饭
Even mushroom risotto?
甚至蘑菇意大利饭
What do you think?!
你想什么呢
So...
这个
...how'd we do?
我们表现得怎样
Not as bad as the worst school
in the state.
同比之下不是很差
Oh, thank God.
哦，太好了
You did worse than the worst school in the state,
你们是比最差还差的学校
which now makes this school
这是哪个学校
the worst school in the state.
该州里最差的学校
Why did you say that to us in the meanest way you could?
为什么你不告诉我们，直接用最坏的方式
To show you that there's no way out.
为了让你们没有路走
Except...Except what?
除非，除非什么
No, I meant you should accept your terrible fate.
没有，我意思是让你们接受这个事实
Oh.
哦
This place is worse
这个地方很差劲
than the elementary school in prison.
比不上监狱里的小学
This student filled in everything but the ovals.
这个孩子填写了每个地方，除了椭圆内
In art school he'd be a genius.
在艺术学校也许是个天才
This isn't an art school.
这可不是个艺术学校
We tried to have ourselves accredited as one,
我们尝试让我们接受这个
but no one here could,uh, draw the pirate.
但是没有一个人能，呃，画那个海盗
Children, Groundskeeper Willie will direct you
孩子们，管理员willie将会指导你们
to your new school district.
去你们的新校区
Any correlation to your talents,needs, or friends
任何有关你们的天赋，需求，或朋友
is completely coincidental.
都是巧合
Sherri, you're going to West Ogdenville.
sherri，你准备好去西 ogdenville
Terri, North Haverbrook.
terri，南haverbrook
But we've never been separated.
但是我们从不分开
I'm not sure we can even live apart.
我不确信我们能分开生活
Stop your whinging.
不准唠叨
It's not like you're losing a rake or a backhoe.
这才不像你失去了耙子或拖拉机一样
Nelson, you're off to Arkham Elementary School
nelson，你该去arkham 小学
for the Criminally Insane.
由于你疯狂的罪行
Well, I'm glad you're not upset.
好吧，我很高兴你不是很沮丧
All my extra credit points are like
我所有的额外加分如同
frequent flyer miles on a bankrupt airline.
一个破产的航空之旅
Hey, don't blame me.I didn't even take the test.
嘿，干嘛怪我，我甚至没考试
You didn't?
你没有
Is there no limit to your disrespect?
没有限制你无礼
Eh, I had something better to do.
哦，我有更好的事去做
Driving you crazy instead of pulling off your legs.
操控你而不用抓着你的腿
I've really matured.
我已经长大了
Wait a minute.
等等
If you take the test now,your score could raise
如果你现在去考试，你的分数会提高
the average and save the school.
平均数并且拯救学校
Proctor Clarkson, one student still hasn't taken the test.
clarkson学督，有个学生没考试。
Let it be Martin,let it be Martin.
但愿是martin，但愿是martin
It's Bart.
是bart
I have an aunt named Hope.
我有个姑妈叫希望
Perhaps you'd like to kill her as well.
也许你也想杀了她
Bart will take his exam
bart会考试的
first thing tomorrow morning.
明天早上第一件事
Bart, I'm begging you to try and study.
bart，我求你试着学习呗
When I think begging, I don't imagine someone standing up.
当我认为有人求的时候，我不喜欢站着的
Sorry, I can't grant a favor
抱歉，我不能答应
to someone I don't respect anymore.
某些我不尊重的人
You can spin in my chair!
你可以转我的椅子
Whee!
whee
Spinner!Slow down.
转椅，慢下来
Well, sure the Lord wouldn't have placed his meter there
好吧，相信上帝不会在这留地方
if he didn't want me to park.
倘若他不想我在这停车
This is the easiest money I've ever made.
这是最简单的来钱方式
Lugging around a 90-pound parking meter.
拖着近50磅的停车计时器
It's not that kind.
这不友好
All right, now to drag the meter to the next idiot.
好吧，现在拖着个计时器去找下一个白痴吧
Oh, God, my back.
哦，天啊，我的后背
Suckers.
衰人
Oh, my disks are grinding.
哦，我的圆盘正在摩擦
Easy money.
简单挣钱
♪ Ch-Ch-Ch-Ch-Changes
改改改改变
♪ Turn and face the strange ch-ch-changes ♪
转变和面对陌生的改变
♪ Don't wanna be a richer man
不想成为一个更富的人
♪ Ch-Ch-Ch-Ch-Changes
改改改改变
♪ Turn and face the strange ch-ch-changes. ♪
不想成为一个更富的人
Thanks for the freedom of speech, dorks.
感谢言论自由，笨蛋
Uh, we're cool, right, boy?
哦，我们很酷，对吗
Nothing a few George Washingtons won't solve.
没有华盛顿不能解决的
Now, to sleep the sleep of the just.
现在，在刚要睡觉的睡觉
Godspeed, old chum.
一路顺风，老朋友
Pass the test and your lunch money is yours.
通过考试你的午餐钱就是你的了
I'm a kid you've never seen,and I speak for all
我是一个你从未见过的孩子，并且为所有
the kids you've never seen.
你没见过的孩子说
Do it, man, or you'll never see us again.
去考试吧，男人，你将不会再次见到我
Principal Skinner, could you help me sharpen this pencil?
（考场）skinner校长，你能帮我削铅笔吗
I guess a little circular grinding might relax me.
我猜有点圆的会让我放松
I can't do this.I'm not ready.
我不都能考试，我没准备好
You really didn't study?
你真的没学习？
Well, I slept on my books,
好吧，我在书上睡着了
so I might have gotten something through osmosis.
我也许潜移默化中做了什么
So, you know what osmosis is?
所以，你了解什么是潜移默化？
Uh, pajamas?
嗯，睡衣
Let me make this crystal clear to you, Simpson.
让我用水晶清醒你把，simpson
If you don't pass this test,
如果你没通过考试
it will destroy the school.
将会毁了学校
Our entire school riding on that coffee can head of yours.
我们全学校的咖啡都取决于你了
We've got to get you more time to study.
我们得为你争取更多时间去学习
But how?
但是该怎么做
Pull the fire alarm.
拉火警器
I'd do it,but everyone's looking at me.
我要是做了，每个人都会看着我
What to do, what to do?
该做什么，该做什么
Don't do it, Seymour.
不要，seymour
You've never broken school rules. Ever.
你绝不能破坏学校的规定，绝不
You wimp.
懦弱的家伙
Children, remain calm,find your disaster buddy,
孩子们，保持冷静，找到你的难友
which is different from your lab partner
这不同于你的实验伙伴
but may be the same as your lunchroom buddy.
但是也许如同你的午饭伙伴
Well, well, well...
好吧好吧
Looks like Mr. Vanilla just grew some chocolate chips.
看起来像vanilla先生刚长出巧克力棒
Save your analogies for the analogy portion of the exam.
留着你的推论在模拟考试吧
I bought you time, boy.Don't blow it.
给你时间，孩子，别浪费了
I won't.
我不会了
I'm going to ignore everything else on my schedule.
我准备忽略所有事除了我的学习表
Pass this test and the eggs are on me.
通过考试和扔我鸡蛋
They will be, Seymour. They will be.
他们会实现的，seymour，他们会实现的
I'm king of the bus station.
我对客运站很友好
Meter, meter,quarter cheater?
计价器，计价器，骗子一枚
A rogue parking meter has been terrorizing the streets.
恐怕在街上出现了一个流氓停车计价器
Experts estimate the cost to taxpayers at north of $50.
专家估计其花费超过北美纳税50美元
That's right, Kent.
好吧，kent
The entire force is on the lookout for anyone
全部的武力都投入侦察
with an excessive amount of change.
由于过量改变
Our top criminologists have a theory
我们最顶尖的犯罪学家有个说法
as to what the suspect just might look like.
犯罪嫌疑人也许看起来像这个样子
But, of course,that question mark could be
但是，好吧，罪人可能会标记为
an exclamation point or an interrobang.
一个感叹号或疑问感叹号
And the man or woman could be Hispanic or,
或是男人或女人或西班牙人
most frightening,contain no punctuation at all.
最可怕的是没有任何标点符号
So, how's the studying going?
好吧，学的咋样了
When I start I'll tell you.
我开始时会告诉你的
This is the most selfish thing you've ever done.
这是你有史以来最自私的事了
You're letting your friends go hang because you
你让你的朋友挂掉由于你
are lazy and selfish and, hey,are you falling asleep
的懒惰和自私，嘿，你困了
just to spite me?
只是厌恶我吗
Hey, why aren't you eating that?
嘿，为什么你不吃这个
There's four of us and eight slices.
有4个人，而这有8块
We don't know how to divide it.
我们不知道怎么去分
Something Stu forgot the music he loves.
有些学生忘了他喜爱的音乐了
Mrs. Krabappel?Are you a teacher of the night?
krabappel女士，你是晚间老师了
Ha, I wish I was a hooker.
哈，我希望我是妓女
No one in this town has any money.
这个城市没有有钱人
But the worst thing is what's happened to the school.
然而最坏的事是学校所发生的
No, no!
不
What have I done?
我做了什么
Spinach farm, huh?
菠菜农场，呃
That's right,you talk in your sleep.
好吧，你说梦话了
Lisa, I want to pass that test.
lisa 我想通过考试
But I need your help.
我需要你的帮助
I have all sorts of problems:
我有很多问题
Lack of attention,I'm afraid of ovals,
集中精力，我还怕椭圆形
I only know 24 letters.
我只知道24个字母
Don't you fall asleep on me.
别在我面前睡着了
Excuse me,you're that proctor
打扰了，你是那个学监
that's shutting down my children's school.
那个想关闭我孩子学校的
I don't shut anything down.
我不想关闭任何一个
People cut their own heads,
这是他们自己自绝的
and I just tip 'em into the basket.
我只是来清理到篮子里而已
You've been in public education a long time, haven't you?
你在公共教育领域很长时间，不是吗
Freeze,Jack Nickel-scum.
冻结吧，jack nickel-scum
Wha...?
啥
You know what they do to parking meter thieves in prison?
你知道在监狱里他们做计价器盗贼
They probably treat 'em pretty well.
他们可能对他们很好
But when you get out, you're not eligible for jury duty.
但是当你出狱，你不适合做陪审员
Which, again,sounds pretty good.
哪个，重复下，听起来不错
Eat silver, copper.
吃我硬币把
D'oh!
不
Stay with me, man.
别挂，基友
Stay with me.
别挂了
No, no!
不（已断气）
You're the first successful business I've ever run.
你是我从未超过的成功商人
It's hopeless.
没救了
I can't make up for ten years of goofing off in one day.
我做不到用一天来弥补十年的消磨
I need two days.
我需要两天
Look, the thing is, it's more important to know
看，事情如此，这是更重要的去了解
how to take a test than knowing what's on it.
如何选择答案比知道选项是什么更重要
So do the ones you know first.
好了，来做第一个你该知道的
If you don't know one,guess "B" and move on.
如果你不知道，就去猜B或扩展选项
Now, what is the capital of Massachusetts?
现在，马塞诸塞州的首府是什么
Uh, "B"?
呃，b
Very good.
对头
Okay, this is it. Do or die.
好吧，就是它，生或死
D'oh. Will you stop that?
天啊，你能听下来吗（专心致志）
Burly Paper Towels, Burlyville, Minnesota.
身材魁梧的擦手纸，身材魁梧的市政厅，明尼苏达州。
Dear Sir or Madam:
亲爱的先生或女士
Your paper towel packets promised 102 sheets of towels.
你的纸包说是有102卷
But I was blessed to receive 103.
但是我很幸运的收到了103卷
I'm returning the extra towel, unused...
这张额外的一卷，未使用
Hmm?
呃
A pillow case full of quarters?
一枕头的硬币
Where did you get that money?
你从哪来的钱
And what have you done with the pillows?
你要做什么用着一枕头
The pillows are safe at my workstation.
在我工作区枕头是安全的
As for the quarters, well,
作为硬币，好吧
I'm ashamed to tell you what I did.
我很惭愧的告诉你我将做什么
How long have you been in there?
你在这多久了
Well, we're going to turn this change
好吧，我们去做点事吧
into change for the better.
去变得更好
Whoo-hoo!
喔
And I wish that Mr. Teeny gets a banana,
我祝愿tenny先生能得到香蕉
that the Isotopes emerge from this season
从这个季度的同位素球队那
with a great blooper reel.
一个大的花圈
I wish that wishing wells worked
我希望愿望都实现
so I wasn't tossing my money away
还有我不想到处扔我的钱
and that Marge loves me forever
还有marge永远爱我
no matter what stupid things I do.
无论我做了多愚蠢的事
And I hope Bart passes his test and saves the school.
还有我希望bart通过考试，挽救学校
Way to get us back on topic, Marge.
让我们回到主题上，marge
If you have to guess, guess "B."
如果你必须猜，猜“b”
Not every question!
不是所有问题
The second that boy fails, we're knocking down this school.
那家伙再不及格，我们就只有拆学校了
Please have a little faith.
还是自信点吧
I hear you, Seymour.
我听到了，seymour
Start the upswing!
开始准备吧
The least common blood type is A) B,
最常见的血型是A或B
B) A, C) AB,
B A C AB
D) O... d'oh! Ten more seconds.
D，不，还剩10秒
And the last answer, "C."
最后一道题是C
Is correct.
对了
Congratulations, you made it by one.
恭喜，你一次通过了
That'll do, bug, that'll do.
做你想做的吧，虫子，做你想做
He passed.
他通过了
Stop that ball!
停下那个球
Now your mom can see you work from her house.
现在你妈妈能从家看到你工作了
Seymour, stop slouching!
seymour，不要无精打采
I'm not sure if you gave my son any extra help,
我不确信，你是否给了我儿子特别的帮助
but if you did, thank you.
但是倘若如此，谢谢
Perhaps this was a test of my humanity.
也许这是我人生中的一个测试
A test I like to think I passed.
一个测试，我想我通过了
Would you like to have coffee or dinner, or just talk?
喝点咖啡或吃点饭，或是聊聊天
None of the above.
不必了
Testward ho!
奔向测试，哦
Is this Wilson Elementary?
这是威尔逊小学吗
No. Sorry.
不，抱歉
偷停车计价器的行为：A）一个不法行为 B）一个重罪 C）一个愚蠢的挣钱方式D）FOX电台建立的基石
Shh!